myfirstmobileapp.com 2017-03-12

# Privacy Policy of a Mobile Application Development Company | MyFirstMobileApp

The issue of online privacy is extremely crucial for MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP which is committed to safeguarding the information provided by its members and other visitors logging on to its Web site. As an organization dedicated to offering professional web & mobile application development services world, MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP has been actively promoting the concept of privacy and its relevance for organizations with a cyber-presence. 

Respecting the privacy of its online visitors while providing top-of-the-line services to customers has remained the core of MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP’s strategy. Our Privacy Policy gives visitors a view of the Privacy Practices followed by MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP and assures them of safe passage through the organization’s Web site. 

At the same time, MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP would like to make it clear that its site provides links to other Web sites that are governed by their own Privacy Policies and does not take responsibility for the security provided by these sites. Visitors to the MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP site are urged to familiarize themselves with their respective Privacy Policies. 

When you provide us with your personal data, you are agreeing to the rules and regulations stipulated under our Privacy Policy and are bound by it. If you do not agree to our Policy please do not use the Site.

#### The Privacy Policy covers the following areas: 

  * Type of information collected through the Web site 
  * Use and Disclosure of personal information 
  * Choice or Opt out 
  * Security 

#### 1\. Type of information collected through the Web site

##### Personal information

Users visiting MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP website and providing information at the MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP site for specific services are requested to provide some personally identifiable information which becomes the property of MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP and can be shared, disclosed or distributed to third parties only in accordance with the Privacy Policy. It must be clarified here that providing information is not required for visitors to the site who do not require any specific services. 

#### 2\. Use and Disclosure of personal information

MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP will not sell or rent such personally identifiable information collected. The personally identifiable information is supplied voluntarily for some of the following purposes: 

##### Data:

If you are merely a visitor to our site, MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP does not collect any personal information about you, except to the limited extent through the use of cookies and IP address details. If you decide to enquire about certain services offered on the site, you will be asked to provide basic online contact information about yourself. 

##### E-mail information:

When we receive e-mails from you, we may retain the content of any e-mail messages sent to us, as well as details of your e-mail address. 

##### Use of web-based tracking mechanisms such as Cookies

Cookies, which enable us to store small amounts of information contained in your Web site browser, may be used on some areas of our Website. Cookies, that help us track your navigation, enable us to tailor our offerings to your needs. 

Third party Websites which are accessible from our Site via links, click-throughs or banner advertising may use Cookies. However, it is important for us to inform you that we have no access or control over such Cookies and do not accept responsibility with regards to them. 

#### 3\. Choice OR opt out

MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP gives you the choice regarding the collection and usage of your personally identifiable information. Again, it is not necessary for you to provide any information in order to access and use our Site. _ **You may therefore choose to opt out of providing such information.**_

Further, once you provide information at the MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP site, you will have the option at any stage to inform us that you no longer wish to receive future e-mails and you may unsubscribe by sending a simple email with the subject UNSUBSCRIBE. 

#### 4\. Security Practices As per I.T.Act, 2000 and Rules of I.T.Act, 2000 (Upgraded as per Amendment in I.T.Act, 2000)

MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP has implemented stringent, reasonably acceptable standards of technology and operational security in order to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. The data resides behind a firewall, with access restricted to authorized MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP personnel. 

MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP has implemented “Reasonable Security Practices” as required by the Information Technology Act, 2000 rules including any amendment in the said Act and its rules. By complying with such provisions, MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP assures proper care and control over its I.T. and Security operations under sections 43, 43A, 45 & Section 85 of I.T.Act, 2000 including related rules and thus you agree and acknowledge that MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP shall not be held responsible for any cyber crime activity relating to your data. 

By using this site you agree and acknowledge that MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP shall not be held responsible for any uncontrollable security attack and in such cases you agree that MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP shall not be held responsible for any type of financial, opportunity, legal, business (lost profits) and reputation losses that may occur to you under the Provisions of Section 43, 43A and 45 of Information Technology Act, 2000 and including any amendments in the said Act. 

You further agree that MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP top management shall not be held responsible directly or indirectly for any cyber-crime related criminal liabilities under I.T.Act,2000 relating to your information as you agree and acknowledge that Top management of MYFIRSTMOBILEAPP complies with due diligence requirements of I.T.Act,2000 including its rules and amendments. 

##### Contacting the web site 

For questions regarding the privacy statement, practices of the site, or any other transaction issue, please contact 

##### Amendments to these Policies 

We are serving the right to amend these policies from time to time. When we make a change we will update this page of the Website. We recommend that you revisit this page from time to time so as to ensure that you are aware of any changes that we have made to these Policies.
